TERENCE ONYEKACHI

27 Mafoluku road, Oshodi, Lagos State · +2347085429640

<u>Terenceonyekachi@gmail.com</u> · <u>www.linkedin.com/in/terence-onyekachi-23baa7210</u> · <u>https://twitter.com/terencino8</u> . <u>www.github.com/Terencino8/</u>

I.t. Support Engineer with 1 Year Experience in the use of Figma in creating responsive User Interfaces Office 365 administration, Network configuration and administration skills, Knowledge in networking hardwares and protocols, Excellent client relation skills, troubleshooting and repairs of computer hardware, Excellent communication skills, I believe that I have the qualities and experience required to be a suitable candidate for your company.

EXPERIENCE

FROM APRIL 2021 - SEPTEMPER 2021

SOFTWARE/HARDWARE ENGINEER INTERN, REDSTAR PLC HEADQUATER

While working in Redstar Plc FedEx,

- I worked with software engineers in updating the companies website which improved the speed of page by 15% after implementation.
- Helped out in repairs and troubleshooting of network servers.
- Worked with other of my intern colleagues in producing a web app.

FROM MARCH 2022 – OCTOBER 2022

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, REDSTAR PLC HEADQUATER

- Currently help out with front end development, web / app designs for as a side project in the company.
- Currently, I Volunteered to teaching new incoming junior interns to the company, taking them on basic web programming foundations.
- Successfully help in preparing reports, spreadsheets and memos.
- Created 5 [five] different User Interfaces and experience.

EDUCATION

NOVEMBER -2016 TILL 2021

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY, FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY, OWERRI, IMO STATE [FUTO].

SEPTEMBER – 2010 TILL JULY - 2016
S.S.C.E, COMMAND DAY SCONDARY SCHOOL, OSHODI, LAGOS STATE.

SKILLS

- Intermediate proficiency in Hardware Engineering
- Intermediate proficiency in UI/UX, Figma and Adobe XD,
- Intermediate proficiency in Html 5, CSS bootstrap and materialize
- Intermediate Proficiency in JavaScript, and React Js.
- basic proficiency in Python

ACTIVITIES

Currently undergoing two certified courses on coursera and side hustle.

Created little semi projects found on my github at intern level.

At my spare time, I enjoy playing basketball, singing and listening to music.

Organizing and playing in basketball competitions in my local community.

Organized a concert with a group of students in raising funds for my school chapel through singing.